# Yasmin Fatteh

Ahmedabad. India fatteh.win@gmail.com

+91-9979566855 www.linkedin.com/in/yasmin-fatteh

# **Yasmin Fatteh**

#### M.B.A with Finance

An enthusiastic and dedicated M.B.A post graduate with over 10 years' experience in the Banking, Pharmaceuticals, Insurance and IT industry.

Extremely organized with the ability to work both independently of own initiative or as part of a successful team, demonstrating the motivation and multi-tasking abilities required to meet requirements from the employer while maintaining the highest of standards.

Combines a professional and confident approach with excellent interpersonal skills and can communicate concisely at all levels. Currently looking for a new and challenging position as an Admin, Operational or Human Resource Department.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Sr. Human Resource & Admin Executive Europa Healthcare Pvt. Ltd. June 2019– Present

(Europa is a young pharmaceutical company and one of the trusted names in pharmaceutical industry small venture in India, especially in Gujarat/ MP/ Mumbai.

- Payroll and attendance management,
- Employee leave management.
- PF / ESI Compliance issue and number generation
- Maintain PF and ESI Challan and payment receipt
- Provident fund and employee state insurance compliance.
- MIS reports, Performance appraisal management. Full and final settlement Process,
- Employee Joining and exit formalities
- Employee tax calculation
- Generate Offer and Appointment letter
- Salary Account Opening of employee process
- Medical and Accidental Insurance process.
- Field employee Expenses claim settlement
- Filed employee Doctor list, routes upload into EBMS system
- Reporting unlock- EBMS
- Administration activities i.e petty cash, office equipment management.
- Courier Management
- Recruitment (from consultant / Naukri Portal and employee reference)
- Events Management
- Forming and maintaining employee records.
- Updating databases internally, such as sick and maternity leave.
- Preparing and amending where necessary HR documents, i.e. employment contracts and recruitment guides.

Reviewing and renewing company policies and legal compliance.

## Sr. Human Resource Executive <u>Inizia Healthcare Pvt. Ltd.</u> Aug 2016– June-19

(Inizia is a young pharmaceutical company and one of the trusted names in pharmaceutical industry in India. .

- Payroll and attendance management, Employee leave management.
- Provident fund and employee state insurance compliance issue needs to be sort out.
- MIS reports, Performance appraisal management. Full and final settlement Process,
- Employee Joining and exit formalities
- Employee tax calculation
- Generate Offer and Appointment letter
- Bank Account Opening of employee process
- Medical and Accidental Insurance process.

# Sr. Payroll & HRMS Executive Orange Techno lab Mar 2014 – Aug 216

(Orange Techno lab is a global Software Development Company providing IT solutions to companies worldwide)

- Web payroll support
- HRMS support
- Time/ Attendance Management
- Follow up with clients for employee details like new joining, left employees.
- Give training on payroll (the whole HRMS process online) to clients of the Organization i.e.
  Orange Techno lab
- Joining Process
- Making employee data like hiring, and shortfall / attrition ratio of the Organization.
- Product implementation

# Human Resource &

Admin Co-Ordinator MetLife Insurance Pvt. Ltd Sep 2010 – Feb 2014

(MetLife Insurance, amongst the trusted Life Insurance companies in India, aims to provide a wide range of Life Insurance products that suits the needs of an individual at every stage of his life.)

- MIS Reports of individual employee sales.
- Business reports including sales growth, comparison between month on month and year to year.

- Employee reimbursements BTER (Business Travel Expenses Report) process from the approval till the payment released.
- Hotel and travel tickets booking as per the requirement and approved amount per designation.
- Administrative and operational responsibilities.
- Sales Co-ordination
- Co- ordination with other Branch of the Organization

### **EDUCATION & PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT**

**Post-Graduation Degree- MBA with Finance** North Gujarat University: Grade: - 3.17/4.00. 67 %

Mar 2004 – Jun 2006

**Graduation Degree- B.Com** North Gujarat University: Grade: - 73 % *Mar* 2002 – *Jun* 2004

#### Courses:

Certified course in computer (CIC)

#### Software skills:

- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- Microsoft outlook
- Excel expertly i.e. vlook up, graph
- Presentation
- Typing.

### Personal details:

DOB:- 3<sup>rd</sup> Sept 1983

Languages known-. English, Hindi, Gujarati

Mail I'd-. fatteh.win@gmail.com

Cell-. 9979566855.

**Declaration:** I hereby declare that particulars given herein are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Name: Yasmin Fatteh.